// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the change in the angular momentum of a system as per the Law of Conservation of Angular momentum, if the total external torque acting is zero?",
        answer: "Remains constant",
        options: [
            "Remains constant",
            "Becomes zero",
            "Increases exponentiall",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following conditions is true for an object to be in equilibrium?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "No linear motion of the object",
            "No rotational motion of the object",
            "Minimum potential energy of the object",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "As per the Newton’s second law of motion, what is the relation between the rate of change of linear momentum and the external force applied?",
        answer: "inversely proportional",
        options: [
            "directly proportional",
            "inversely proportional",
            "independent of each other",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "On which of the following quantities, Work done does not depend?",
        answer: "Time",
        options: [
            "Force applied",
            "Displacement",
            "Time",
            "Depends on all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "By how much times the orbital speed of a satellite needs to be increased to make it escape the gravitational field?",
        answer: "√2 times",
        options: [
            "√3 times",
            "4 times",
            "2 times",
            "√2 times"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following relations between Kinetic energy and Potential energy is true about solids?",
        answer: "Kinetic energy < Potential energy",
        options: [
            "Kinetic energy = potential energy",
            "Kinetic energy > Potential energy",
            "Kinetic energy >> Potential energy",
            "Kinetic energy < Potential energy"
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "On which of these factors, the buoyancy depends?",
        answer: "Both a and b",
        options: [
            "Density of the fluid",
            "Volume of the body",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following factors affect the Surface Tension?",
        answer: "Nature of liquid",
        options: [
            "Nature of liquid",
            "Area of Surface",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the unit of surface tension in c.g.s system?",
        answer: "dyne/cm",
        options: [
            "N/m",
            "dyne/cm",
            "erg/cm",
            "dyne cm"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What of the following represents viscosity?",
        answer: "resistance to fluid motion",
        options: [
            "resistance to fluid motion",
            "pressure difference between two fluids",
            "potential energy stored in a fluid",
            "roughness of the surface"
        ]
    },
];